Now when I go to unstructured format, we have log files here,
audio files, videos and images. So these are all considered
as unstructured files and sorrel. It is
also because of the speed of accumulation of all this variety
of data altogether, which brings us to our third
v which is velocity. So if you look here earlier we were.
Now let's focus on the diagram. So here you can notice that the hard
disk capacity is increasing but the disk transfer
performance or speed is not. Speed is not a lot of data.
And when you talk about people generating data or Internet reshma,
the one kind of application that strikes first in my mind is social media.
So you tell me. You tell me. You tell me. You tell me.
Thank you and have a great day. I hope you
enjoyed listening to this video. Please be kind enough to like it and you
can comment any of your doubts and queries and we will reply to them at
the reply to them at the reply to them at the reply to them at
the reply to them at the reply to them at the.